Finding Aid for the J. Paul Getty Trust Inventory of Getty Publications, 1954-2013 and undated IA10020
Institutional Records and Archives
- J. Paul Getty Museum, 1954-2000; 2003-2013,; undated; Series I.
  - Seydl, Jon L. Giambattista Tiepolo, Fifteen Oil Sketches. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-17)
  - Sider, David. The Library of the Villa dei Papyri at Herculaneum. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-18)
  - Sotirakopoulou, Peggy. The "Keros Hoard": Myth or Reality?: Searching for The Lost Pieces of a Puzzle. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 2006.IA.01-02)
  - Thesaurus Cultus et Rituum Antiquorum (ThesCRA) I: Processions; Sacrifices; Libations; Fumigations; Dedications. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 2012.IA.01-38)
  - Thesaurus Cultus et Rituum Antiquorum (ThesCRA) II: Purification; Initiation; Heroization; Apotheosis; Banquet; Dance; Music; Cult Images. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 2012.IA.01-38)
  - Thesaurus Cultus et Rituum Antiquorum (ThesCRA) III: Divination; Prayer; Veneration; Hikesia; Asylia; Oath; Maldediction; Profanation; Magic Rituals; and Addendum to Vol. II: Consecration. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 2012.IA.01-37)
  - Thesaurus Cultus et Rituum Antiquorum (ThesCRA) IV: Cult Places; Representations of Cult Places. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 2012.IA.01-37)
  - Thesaurus Cultus et Rituum Antiquorum (ThesCRA) V: Personnel of Cult; Cult Instruments. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 2012.IA.01-37)
  - Thesaurus Cultus et Rituum Antiquorum (ThesCRA): Abbreviations. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 2012.IA.01-38)
    Cover: soft cover.
  - Thesaurus Cultus et Rituum Antiquorum (ThesCRA): Abbreviations; Index of Museums, Collections and Sites. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 2012.IA.01-38)
    Cover: Hard cover.
  - True, Marion, and Jorge Silvetti. The Getty Villa. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 2012.IA.01-26)
  - Woff, Richard. A Pocket Dictionary of Ancient Greek Heroes and Heroines. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-17)
  - Zuffi, Stefano. European Art of the Fifteenth Century. Translated by Brian D. Phillips. Los Angeles: 2005. (Box 1987.IA.04-19)
  - Beckett, Wendy. Joy Lasts: On the Spiritual in Art. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2006.IA.01-01)
  - Bezanilla, Clara. A Pocket Dictionary of Aztec and Mayan Gods and Goddesses. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2012.IA.01-05)
  - Bischoff, Ulrich, Elisabeth Hipp, Jeanne Anne Nugent. From Caspar David Friedrich to Gerhard Richter: German Paintings from Dresden. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2012.IA.01-17)
  - Brooks, Julian. Guercino: Mind to Paper. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2006.IA.01-02)
  - Cohen, Beth. The Colors of Clay: Special Techniques in Athenian Vases. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2006.IA.01-03)
  - Cohen, Beth. The Colors of Clay: Special Techniques in Athenian Vases. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2008.IA.01-03)
  - Franits, Wayne. Pieter de Hooch: A Woman Preparing Bread and Butter for a Boy. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2007.IA.01-01)
  - Fuga, Antonella. Artists' Techniques and Materials. Translated by Rosanna M. Giammanco Frongia. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2006.IA.01-02)
  - Giusti, Annamaria. Pietre Dure: The Art of Semiprecious Stonework. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2006.IA.01-03)
  - Goldman, Paul. Looking at Prints, Drawings and Watercolours: A Guide to Technical Terms. London: 2006. (Box 2006.IA.01-01)
  - Goldman, Paul. Looking at Prints, Drawings and Watercolours: A Guide to Technical Terms. London: 2006. (Box 2007.IA.01-01)
  - Kahsnitz, Rainer. Carved Splendor: Late Gothic Altarpieces in Southern Germany, Austria, and South Tirol. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box Shared 2006.IA.01-04; 2008.IA.01-06)
  - Keller, Judith and Anne Lacost. Where We Live: Photographs of America, from the Berman Collection. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box Shared 2006.IA.01-04; 2008.IA.01-06)
  - Lancret, Nicolas. Dance Before a Fountain. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2006.IA.01-01)
  - Morrison, Elizabeth and Thomas Kren. Flemish Manuscript Painting in Context: Recent Research. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2007.IA.01-01)
  - Morton, Mary and Charlotte Eyerman. Courbet and the Modernist Landscape. Los Angeles, 2006. (Box 2006.IA.01-03)
  - Nelson, Robert S. and Kristen M. Collins. Holy Image, Hallowed Ground: Icons from Sinai. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2007.IA.01-01)
  - Outram, Dorinda. Panorama of the Enlightenment. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2007.IA.01-01)
  - Rao, Sirish and Gita Wolf. Euripides' Hippolytos. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2006.IA.01-02)
  - Roberts, Paul. A Pocket Dictionary of Roman Emperors. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2006.IA.01-01)
  - Steingraber, Stephan. Abundance of Life: Etruscan Wall Painting. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box Shared 2006.IA.01-04; 2008.IA.01-06)
  - Thesaurus Cultus et Rituum Antiquorum (ThesCRA): Abbreviations. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2011.IA.01-02)
  - Tradigo, Alfredo. Icons and Saints of the Eastern Othodox Church. Translated by Stephen Sartarelli. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2006.IA.01-01)
  - Vreeland, Frederick, and Vanessa Vreeland. Key to Rome. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2006.IA.01-01)
  - Woollett, Anne T. and Ariane van Suchtelen. Rubens & Brueghel: A Working Friendship. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2006.IA.01-03)
  - Zuffi, Stephano. European Art of the Sixteenth Century. Translated by Antony Shugaar. Los Angeles: 2006. (Box 2006.IA.01-01)
  - Abbott, Brett, ed. Edward Weston's Book of Nudes. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2007.IA.01-02)
  - Baragli, Sandra. European Art of the Fourteenth Century. Translated by Brian D. Phillips. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2007.IA.01-01)
  - Battistini, Matilde. Astrology, Magic, and Alchemy in Art. Translated by Rosanna M. Giammanco Frongia. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2007.IA.01-01)
  - Brooks, Julian. Taddeo and Federico Zuccaro: Artist-Brothers in Renaissance Rome. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2012.IA.01-26)
  - Daehner, Jens, Kordelia Knoll, Christiane Vorster, and Mortiz Woelk. The Herculaneum Women, History, Context, Identities. Los Angeles and Dresden: 2007 (Box 2007.IA.01-02)
  - Gardner Coates, Victoria C., and John L. Seydl, eds. Antiquity Recovered: The Legacy of Pompeii and Herculaneum. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2007.IA.01-02)
  - Gelber, Lisa and Jody Roberts. P is for Peanut: A Photographic A-B-C. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2007.IA.01-02)
  - Gilman, Benedicte. Ashen Sky: The Letters of Pliny the Younger on the Eruption of Vesuvius. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2007.IA.01-02)
  - Great Moments in Greek Archaeology. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2007.IA.01-01)
  - Heilmeyer, Marina. Ancient Herbs. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2007.IA.01-02)
  - Holmes, Mary Tavener. My Travels with Clara. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2007.IA.01-02)
  - Humble, John. A Place in the Sun: Photographs of Los Angeles by John Humble. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2007.IA.01-02)
  - Impelluso, Lucia. Gardens in Art. Translated by Stephen Sartarelli. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2007.IA.01-01)
  - The J. Paul Getty Museum, Handbook of the Collections. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2007.IA.01-02)
  - Keller, Judith. Graciela Iturbide: Juchitán. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2007.IA.01-02)
  - Kren, Thomas. French Illuminated Manuscripts in the J. Paul Getty Museum. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2007.IA.01-01)
  - Molotiu, Andrei. Fragonard's Allegories of Love. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2007.IA.01-01)
  - Morrison, Elizabeth. Beasts: Factual & Fantastic. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2007.IA.01-02)
  - Morton, Mary, ed. Oudry's Painted Menagerie: Portraits of Exotic Animals in Eighteenth-Century Europe. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2007.IA.01-02)
  - Ricotti, Eugenia Salza Prina. Meals and Recipes from Ancient Greece. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2012.IA.01-33)
  - Schofield, Louise. The Mycenaeans. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2007.IA.01-01)
  - Schryver, Antoine de. The Prayer Book of Charles the Bold: A Study of a Flemish Masterpiece from the Burgundian Court. Translated by Jessica Berenheim. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2012.IA.01-33)
  - Brooks, Julian, ed. Taddeo and Federico Zuccaro: Artist-Brothers in Renaissance Rome. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2007.IA.01-02)
  - Taplin, Oliver. Pots & Plays: Interactions between Tragedy and Greek Vase-painting of the Fourth Century B.C. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2007.IA.01-01)
  - Trofimvo, Anna, ed. Greeks on the Black Sea: Ancient Art from the Hermitage. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2007.IA.01-02)
  - Wood, Jon, David Hulks, and Alex Potts, eds. Modern Sculpture Reader. Los Angeles: 2007. (Box 2012.IA.01-33)
  - Bacchi, Andrea, Catherine Hess, and Jennifer Montagu eds. Bernini and the Birth of Baroque Portrait Sculpture. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-04)
  - Boström, Antonia, ed. The Fran and Ray Stark Collection of 20th-Century Sculpture at the J. Paul Getty Museum. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-05)
  - Brafman, David and Stephanie Schrader. Insects & Flowers: The Art of Maria Sibylla Merian. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-03)
  - Chatel de Brancion, Laurence. Carmontelle's Landscape Transparencies: Cinema of the Enlightenment. Los Angeles, 2008. (Box 2007.IA.01-02)
  - Curtis, Penelope. Patio and Pavilion: The Place of Sculpture in Modern Architecture. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2012.IA.01-33)
  - Dorleac, Laurence Bertrand. Art of the Defeat, France 1940-1944. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2010.IA.01-04)
  - Furlotti, Barbara and Guido Rebecchini. The Art of Mantua: Power and Patronage in the Renaissance. translated by A. Lawrence Jenkens. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box Shared 2006.IA.01-04; 2008.IA.01-06)
  - Giorgi, Rosa. European Art of the Seventeenth Century. Translated by Rosanna M. Giammanco Frongia. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-04)
  - Giorgi, Rosa. The History of the Church in Art. Translated by Brian Phillips. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-03)
  - Hackman, William, and Mark Greenberg, eds. Inside the Getty. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-04)
  - Hedeman, Anne D. Translating the Past: Laurent de Premierfait and Boccaccio's De Casibus. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-05)
  - Henning, Andreas, and Scott Schaefer, ed. Captured Emotion: Baroque Painting in Bologna, 1575-1725. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-04)
  - Inglis, Erik. Faces of Power & Piety. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-04)
  - Lapatin, Kenneth, ed.Papers on Special Techniques in Athenian Vases. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-04)
  - Malaguzzi, Silvia. Food and Feasting in Art. Translated by Brian Phillips. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-03)
  - Marvin, Miranda. The Language of the Muses: The Dialogue Between Roman and Greek Sculpture. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-04)
  - Naef, Weston. Carleton Watkins in Yosemite. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-04)
  - Panzanelli, Roberta, ed. The Color of Life: Polychromy in Sculpture from Antiquity to the Present. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-03)
  - Podany, Jerry, ed. Advances in Protection of Museum Collections from Earthquake Damage, Papers from a Symposium Held at the J. Paul Getty Museum at the Villa on May 3-4, 2006. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-03)
  - Redford, Bruce. Dilettanti: The Antic and the Antique in Eighteenth-Century England. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-03)
  - Reitsma, Ella. Maria Sibylla Merian & Daughters: Women of Art and Science. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-03)
  - Schryver, Antoine de. The Prayer Book of Charles the Bold: A Study of a Flemish Masterpiece from the Burgundian Court. Translated by Jessica Berenbeim. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-04)
  - Tarabra, Daniela. European Art of the Eighteenth Century. Translated by Rosanna M. Giammanco Frongia. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2008.IA.01-03)
  - Wilson, Gillian. French Furniture and Gilt Bronzes: Baroque and Régence: Catalogue of the J. Paul Getty Museum Collection. Los Angeles: 2008. (Box 2012.IA.01-17)
  - Auricchio, Laura. Adelaide Labeille-Guiard: Artist in the Age of Revolution. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-01)
  - Ausoni, Alberto. Music in Art. Translated by Stephen Sartarelli. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-02)
  - Baldwin, Gordon and Martin Jurgens. Looking at Photographs: A Guide to Technical Terms. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2012.IA.01-05)
  - Bevers, Holm, Lee Hendrix, William W. Robinson, and Peter Shatborn. Drawings by Rembrandt and His Pupils: Telling The Difference. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2010.IA.01-17)
  - Bonanni, Filippo. Techniques of Chinese Lacquer: The Classic Eighteenth-Century Treaties on Asian Varnish. Translated by Flavia Perugini. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-01)
  - De Albentiis, Emidio. Secrets of Pompeii: Everyday Life in Ancient Rome. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-04)
  - De Pascale, Enrico. Death and Resurrection in Art. Translated by Anthony Shugaar. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2008.IA.01-05)
  - Doherty, Tiarna and Anne T. Woollett. Looking At Paintings: A Guide to Technical Terms. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-01)
  - Droth, Martina and Penelope Curtis, eds. Taking Shape: Finding Sculpture in the Decorative Arts: an Exhibition Co-Organised by the Henry Moore Institute, Leeds and the J. Paul Getty Museum, Los Angeles, California. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2008.IA.01-05)
  - Harris, John. Discovering Art: Cats. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2012.IA.01-05)
  - Harris, John. Discovering Art: Dogs. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2012.IA.01-05)
  - Harris, John. Discovering Art: Kids. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2012.IA.01-05)
  - Harrison, Thomas, ed. The Great Empires of the Ancient World. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2010.IA.01-05)
  - Heckert, Virginia A. and Anne Lacoste. Irving Penn: Small Trades. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-04)
  - Helvey, Jennifer. Irises: Vincent Van Gogh in the Garden. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-01)
  - Jenkins, Ian and Victoria Turner. The Greek Body. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2010.IA.01-05)
  - Karraker, D. Gene. Looking at European Frames: A Guide to Terms, Styles, and Techniques. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-01)
  - Keller, Judith. Jo Ann Callis: Woman Twirling. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-02)
  - Kopp, Edouard. Capturing Nature's Beauty: Three Centuries of French Landscapes. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-01)
  - Kren, Thomas. Illuminated Manuscripts of Germany and Central Europe. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-01)
  - Lapatin, Kenneth and Karol Wight, eds. The J. Paul Getty Museum: Handbook of the Antiquities Collection. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2012.IA.01-17)
  - Mornin, Edward and Lorna Mornin. Saints of California: A Guide to Places and Their Patrons. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2010.IA.01-04)
  - Nishimura, Margot McIlwain. Images in the Margins. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-01)
  - Outerbridge, Paul. Command Performance. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-04)
  - Pappalarod, Umberto. The Splendor of Roman Wall Painting. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-02)
  - Politi, Leo. Emmet. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-01)
  - Politi, Leo. Juanita. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-01)
  - Politi, Leo. Pedro: The Angel of Olvera Street. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-01)
  - Politi, Leo. Song of the Swallows. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-01)
  - Roberts, Paul. The Ancient Romans: Their Lives and Their World. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2010.IA.01-04)
  - Schmidt, Eike D. Fruits of Desire: A Seventeenth-Century Carved Ivory Cup. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-01)
  - Seeing the Getty Center: Collections, Buildings and Gardens. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-02)
  - Seeing the Getty Collections at the Getty Center. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-02)
  - Sellier, Marie. Renoir's Colors. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2010.IA.01-04)
  - Slive, Seymour. Rembrandt Drawings. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-02)
  - Williams, Hilary. Rembrandt on Paper. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-01)
  - Woollett, Anne T. Rembrandt in Southern California. Los Angeles: 2009. (Box 2009.IA.01-02)
  - Abbott, Brett. Engaged Observers: Documentary Photography Since the Sixties. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2010.IA.01-17)
  - Bezanilla, Clara. A Pocket Dictionary of Aztec and Mayan Gods and Goddesses. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2010.IA.01-04)
  - Bordin, Giorgio and Laura Polo D'Ambrosio, eds. Medicine in Art. Translated by Jay Hayms. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2011.IA.01-02)
  - Brookes, Julian. Master Drawings Close-Up. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2010.IA.01-05)
  - Clayton, Martin and Ron Philo. Leonardo da Vinci: The Mechanics of Man. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2010.IA.01-05)
  - Corcoran, Lorelei H. and Marie Svobada. Herakleides: A Portrait Mummy from Roman Egypt. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2011.IA.01-01)
  - Freed, Leonard. Black in White America. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2010.IA.01-05)
  - Garcia, Erin C. Photography as Fiction. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2011.IA.01-01)
  - Gonzalez, Marta Alvarez. The Art of Motherhood. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2010.IA.01-04)
  - Hart, Mary Louise. The Art of Ancient Greek Theater. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2011.IA.01-02)
  - Haworth-Booth, Mark. Photographer of Modern Life: Camille Silvy. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2010.IA.01-05)
  - Kren, Thomas. Illuminated Manuscripts from Belgium and the Netherlands. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2011.IA.01-02)
  - Lacoste, Anne. Felice Beato: A Photographer on the Eastern Road. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2011.IA.01-05)
  - Landmann, Bimba. The Incredible Voyage of Ulysses. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2010.IA.01-04)
  - Lyden, Anne M. The Photographs of Frederick H. Evans. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2010.IA.01-13)
  - Malacrino, Carmelo G. Constructing the Ancient World: Architectural Techniques of the Greeks and Romans. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2010.IA.01-04)
  - Martineau, Paul. Still Life in Photography. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2011.IA.01-02)
  - McArthur, Meher. ABC of What Art Can Be. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2010.IA.01-04)
  - Mehring, Christine, Jeanne Anne Nugent and Jon L. Seydl, eds. Gerhard Richter: Early Work, 1951-1972. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2011.IA.01-01)
  - Moorhead, Sam and David Stuttard. AD 410: The Year that Shook Rome. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2011.IA.01-02)
  - Morrison, Elizabeth and Anne D. Hedeman. Imaging the Past in France: History in Manuscript Painting, 1250-1500. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2011.IA.01-05)
  - Pevsner, Nikolaus. Visual Planning and the Picturesque. Edited by Mathew Aitchison. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2010.IA.01-05)
  - Pohl, John M. D. and Claire L. Lyons. The Aztec Pantheon and the Art of Empire. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2010.IA.01-05)
  - Alland, Scott, and Mary Morton, eds. Reconsidering Gerome. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2010.IA.01-04)
  - Reynaud, Francoise. The Tree in Photographs. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2011.IA.01-01)
  - Sciacca, Christine. Building the Medieval World. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2010.IA.01-04)
  - Vercelloni, Matteo and Virgilio Vercelloni. Inventing the Garden. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2011.IA.01-05)
  - Villela, Khristaan D., and Mary Ellen Miller, eds. The Aztec Calendar Stone. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2010.IA.01-05)
  - Villing, Alexandra. The Ancient Greeks: Their Lives and Their World. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2010.IA.01-04)
  - Zanker, Paul. Roman Art. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2011.IA.01-02)
  - Zuffi, Steffano. Love and the Erotic in Art. Los Angeles: 2010. (Box 2010.IA.01-04)
  - Alexander, Christopher James. Julius Shulman's Los Angeles. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-10)
  - Bowe, Patrick and Michael D. Dehart. Gardens and Plants of the Getty Villa. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-01)
  - Bremer-David, Charissa, ed. Paris: Life & Luxury in the Eighteenth Century. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-01)
  - Burnham, Rika and Elliott, Kai-Kee. Teaching in the Art Museum: Interpretation as Experience. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-02)
  - Causey, Faya. Amber and the Ancient World. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2012.IA.01-33)
  - Codrescu, Andrei. Walker Evans: Cuba. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-05)
  - Corbeil, Marie-Claude. Jean Paul Riopelle: the Artist's Materials. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-10)
  - Davis, Robert C. and Beth Lindsmith. Renaissance People: Lives that Shaped the Modern Age. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-07)
  - Fisher, Celia. Flowers of the Renaissance. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-05)
  - Garcia, Erin C. Man Ray in Paris. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-01)
  - Garnier-Pelle, Nicole, Anne Forray-Carlier, Marie-Christine Anselm. The Monkeys of Christophe Huet: Singeries in French Decorative Arts. Translated by Sharon Grevet. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-10)
  - Getty, J. Paul. The Joys of Collecting. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-08)
  - Green, Christopher and Jens M. Daehner. Modern Antiquity: Picasso, De Chirico, Léger, Picabia. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-09)
  - Harris, John and Mark Todd. My Monster Notebook. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-01)
  - Heckert, Virginia. Some Aesthetic Decisions: the Photographs of Judy Fiskin. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-09)
  - Irwin, Robert. Notes Towards a Conditional Art. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-07)
  - Landmann, Bimba. The Fate of Achilles. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-07)
  - Lehmbeck, Leah, ed. Proof: The Rise of Printmaking in Southern California. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-09)
  - Lyons, Martyn. Books: A Living History. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-07)
  - Mayer, Lance and Gay Myers. American Painters: On Technique: the Colonial Period to 1860. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-10)
  - Naef, Weston and Christine Hult-Lewis. Carleton Watkins: The Complete Mammoth Photographs. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-09)
  - Neils, Jennifer. Women in the Ancient World. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-08)
  - Peabody, Rebecca, Andrew Perchuk, Glenn Phillips, and Rani Singh, eds. Pacific Standard Time: Los Angeles Art: 1945-1980. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2013.IA.01-2)
  - Phipps, Elena. Looking at Textiles: A Guide to Technical Terms. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2012.IA.01-33)
  - Rapelli, Paola. Symbols of Power in Art. Translated by Hay Hayms. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-01)
  - Sbriglio, Jaques. Le Corbusier & Lucien Herve: A Dialogue Between Architect and Photographer. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-07)
  - Scott, Margaret. Fashion in the Middle Ages. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-01)
  - Slive, Seymour. Jacob Van Ruisdael: Windmills and Water Mills. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-01)
  - Tummers, Anna. The Eye of the Connoisseur: Authenticating Paintings by Rembrandt and His Contemporaries. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2012.IA.01-33)
  - Warren, Beth Gates. Artful Lives: Edward Weston, Margrethe Mather, and the Bohemians of Los Angeles. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-10)
  - Winckelmann, Johann Joachim. Letter and Report on the Discoveries at Herculaneum. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-07)
  - Woollett, Anne T. Miraculous Bouquets: Flower and Fruit Paintings by Jan van Huysum. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-10)
  - Wright, Karol B. Molten Color: Glassmaking in Antiquity. Los Angeles: 2011. (Box 2011.IA.01-01)
  - Bisanz-Prakken, Marian. Gustav Klimt: The Magic of Line. Los Angeles: 2012. (Box 2012.IA.01-34)
  - Black, Maggie. The Medieval Cookbook, Revised Edition. Los Angeles: 2012. (Box 2012.IA.01-34)
  - Boström, Antonia. Messerschmidt and Modernity. Los Angeles: 2012. (Box 2012.IA.01-34)
  - Dalby, Andrew, and Sally Grainger. The Classical Cookbook, Revised Edition. Los Angeles: 2012. (Box 2012.IA.01-34)
  - Ebert-Schifferer, Sybille. Caravaggio: The Artist and His Work. Los Angeles: 2012. (Box 2012.IA.01-23)
  - Garcia, Erin C. Photography and Play. Los Angeles: 2012. (Box 2012.IA.01-33)
  - Gardner Coates, Victoria C., Kenneth Lapatin, and Jon L. Seydl. The Last Days of Pompeii: Decadence, Apocalypse, Resurrection. Los Angeles: 2012. (Box 2012.IA.01-34)
  - Getty Research Journal: Number 4: 2012. Los Angeles: 2012. (Box 2012.IA.01-34)
  - Hellman, Karen, and Brett Abbott. Landscape in Photographs. Los Angeles: 2012. (Box 2012.IA.01-34)
  - Kesterson, Casie. The Goldfish in the Chandelier. Los Angeles: 2012. (Box 2011.IA.01-09)
  - MacNaughton, Mary Davis, ed. Clay's Tectonic Shift 1956-1968: John Mason, Ken Price, Peter Voulkos. Los Angeles: 2012. (Box 2012.IA.01-34)